# **Addison Moore**

# Full Stack Developer

**LinkedIn**: www.linkedin.com/in/addison-moore **Github**: www.github.com/addisong12 **Website**: http://www.addisonmoore.me

**Phone**: (510) 333-5490

I am a museum curator turned full stack developer, born and raised in the Bay Area. I enjoy camping, board games, and building MERN stack applications. I previously worked as a product designer for an experiential marketing company where I designed custom digital experiences for brands such as Warner Brothers, Nickelodeon, and Facebook. I recently graduated from the Web Development Immersive at General Assembly where I honed my skills as a developer. I'm currently working as a freelance web developer in SF.

#### **SKILLS**

**Languages**: Javascript (ES5, ES6), Python, HTML5, CSS3, French **Server-Side**: MongoDB, Express, Django, Mongoose, PostgreSQL

Frameworks and Libraries: React, React-Native, Node.js, Sass, jQuery, AJAX, JWT

Version Control and Workflow Management: Gihub, Git, Asana, Trello, npm, AGILE, Harvest, Basecamp

**Design**: Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, Figma, Autodesk Fusion 360

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **General Assembly /** Web Development Fellow

OCTOBER 2018 - FEBRUARY 2019, SAN FRANCISCO

I recently graduated General Assembly's 12 week full-time web development immersive, an in depth program that teaches students how to build full stack applications from the ground up, and how to work collaboratively as teams. During the program I work on 5 major projects, 3 collaborative and 2 individual, each using different technologies.

# **The Bosco /** Product Designer, SF Operations Manager

JUNE 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2018, SAN FRANCISCO

- Designed and built core products for The Bosco and custom digital experiences for our clients.
- Launched the Bosco's San Francisco office. Hired and managed the SF team which consisted of at least 10 operations assistants and event staff throughout my tenure.
- Designed over 50 highly custom digital experiences for brands such as Warner Brothers, Nickelodeon, Tommy Hilfiger, Facebook, Sephora.
- Lead designer on new core products including the Bosco Lite and Multicam. These products generated millions in revenue for The Bosco during my time there.

#### **Mendocino County Museum /** Exhibitions Manager

MARCH 2013 - OCTOBER 2015, WILLITS, CA

- Oversaw the installation of exhibitions at the museum and managed the exhibitions team (contractors, volunteers, guest curators, graphic designers, and interns).
- Worked to create engaging exhibitions that used technology to bring the museum into the 21st century.
- Coordinated all parties involved to ensure that exhibitions opened on schedule.

#### **EDUCATION**

**California State University of Monterey Bay**/ Bachelor's Degree - Visual and Public Art AUGUST 2007 - MAY 2012, SEASIDE, CA

At CSU Monterey, I majored in Visual & Public Art with a double concentration in Museum Studies and Sculpture & 3D design. I also acted as director of the Balfour Brutzman Student Gallery.

# Online certificates and courses:

University of Michigan: Python Data Structures

Frontend Masters: Git In-Depth, Introduction to React, Full Stack for Frontend Engineers

Coursera, Udemy: AGILE bootcamp, Beginning Game Programming with C#